[Music]
[音乐]
all comes together photo compulsion to be able to press well if you
如果您愿意，所有人都可以合影。
pre-modern of boring week in crypto's lesson walk the woudestein in 2d
加密课程中无聊的一周的前现代人，在2D中漫步woudestein
so you curse at a free website with king jekyll
所以你在杰基尔国王的免费网站上骂人
and we see that the market square download bates and 6d increases after percent
并且我们看到，在百分比增长之后，市场广场的下载量和6d都增加了
o2 and co2 billion and used all a bit guy went a since last week buys i speak
O2和CO2十亿，用了一点小伙子去了，因为上周买了我说话
clean that is new on sunday's we've got these pictures of clients
清洁，这是星期日的新事物，我们有这些客户的照片
king monkey about him in this case of it for five point to present in a week
在这种情况下，关于他的国王猴在一周之内要展示五点
could be the then site where the gears swimwear
可能是当时装备泳装的地点
lars week but not least one way no no no goodbye at my goals and business to a
拉尔斯周，但并非最不重要的一点，是我对自己的目标和事业的告别
chocolate in flash people at bread and techno what i do things and we recommend
面包店和Techno店里的人们都喜欢吃巧克力，我该怎么做，我们建议
your disco nova client your she writes at the deadline wish something
您的迪斯科新客户，您在截止日期前写的愿望
above you ce why my note in they say what it's very
在您上方，为什么我在他们的笔记中说这很
simple please people or a good cause i say they
简单的请人或一个好的原因，我说他们
do some research very fast reely living expert that can
非常快地做一些研究活着的专家可以
tell you will de marquis corine what's happening you realize
告诉你de marquis corine你会意识到发生了什么
yahoo line then yourself you will head to do the researcher at sqs and manage the
雅虎专线，那么您自己就可以去sqs做研究员并管理
last time to listen to other people and see what der sar
上次听别人说，看什么
but detail and if you have to the research and a promise you today i will
但细节，如果您今天必须进行研究并答应您，我将
show you how to do so research the fortress and who [ __ ] up something with it
告诉你如何做，研究堡垒以及谁用它操了东西
fashion mametchi the fortress yards duo
时尚mametchi的堡垒码二人组
granddeco.com and taboo committee of inquiry is the third best with the motion
granddeco.com和禁忌调查委员会在议案中排名第三
formation and their information is very real abel
阵型和他们的信息是非常真实的亚伯
so it wanted to start you think select a coin that your heart somebody '
因此它想开始您的想法，那就是选择一颗您的心脏某人所需要的硬币
shilling recommending one ever and let's take you for example burns out
先令推荐，让我们举个例子吧
your skin that can i'se gwine so you believe information or the on this page
我可以用酒来保养您的皮肤，以便您相信此信息或此页面上的信息
you neck among other things unless you wet market
除非您湿润市场，否则您会紧缩其他东西
information price information on that is barry woman who farmer when was the all
信息价格信息是所有时候农民的巴里女人
time high yes that also download now on the left hand
时间很高，是的，现在也可以在左侧下载
side ymca duo charge or whatever sahar thing but the trillion mark
副ymca duo负责人或任何萨哈尔事件，但万亿马克
mark j-your sangha application website as far as we allow is up to we go to the
在我们允许的范围内，将j-your sangha应用程序标记为我们的网站
website see what the website cells you have in technical
网站查看您在技术方面拥有哪些网站单元格
details most people than any style by jeecee wants that makes sense of white fracture de
绝大部分人比jeecee想要的任何样式都更有意义，这使白色断裂感更有意义
put money into some body that is promise you something that you to
把钱放到一个可以向你许诺的东西上
student so lets the first in a way to jazz browser our website
学生，所以让第一个以爵士乐方式浏览我们的网站
the all 1-door about you whistle that then see many daring and tanks in you did my
关于您的所有一扇门，然后看到您里面有许多大胆的坦克，
point to some technical things but you can i know right time at the beginning
指出一些技术问题，但您可以在开始时就知道正确的时间
next one is the community so piper icing village in
下一个是社区，所以吹笛者在
you'll want to grab it and tennessee walking dead so you see that something
您将要抓住它，田纳西州要死了，所以您会看到一些东西
was posted 2 days 3 hours ago so whenever one is at one they go
发表于2天3小时前
wall deco saloon sims valley
墙装饰沙龙sims谷
popular in serving sahar thing here next one is twitter twitter is the
在这里服务sahar的事情很流行，下一个是twitter twitter是
central point of communication in the crypt industry so twitter is a must
地穴行业中的通信的中心点，因此必须使用Twitter
have to go in here and so check what the official clear and team in this case
必须去这里，所以在这种情况下检查官方清除和团队
so drink so eat cd publishing
所以喝所以吃CD出版
arcen then go here 20 3 hours ago and there is 20 sec and so after 3 days ago
arcen然后20 3小时前去这里，大约20秒，所以3天前
zoë project active in the marines interviews list do push it in
在海军陆战队采访列表中活跃的zoë项目确实将其推入
rushing was discussion at interview will German blood 'indicator neck disorder
急于在面试中进行讨论将德国血统指标颈部疾病
telegraph telegraph is popular again yoonie ar
电报再次流行yoonie ar
talking enthusiastically open download the telegram a telegram app and to and
热情地交谈打开电报，然后将电报应用下载至
just look into what other people are saying you see a lot of people and there
看看别人在说什么，你会看到很多人
with him super opinions and you see in this case er nighttime emerson
与他的超级意见，你会在这种情况下看到艾默生
home planet you when you are online that they are in the good indicator
当您在线时，您的家乡星球表明它们处于良好状态
enthusiastic miss [ __ ] telegram in this card
这张卡中热情的荡妇小姐电报
simblet a telegram middle ages it still compliqué de the ball complex
simblet电报中世纪仍然补足了复杂的球。
last but not least click on get had microsets where you have series of programmers and
最后但并非最不重要的一点是，单击“获得微型集”，其中有一系列程序员和
working doing their job and here you see sam body updated for one arm red and
工作做他们的工作，在这里您看到山姆身体更新为一只手臂红色和
archivo ccd a very active also in what I do now
Archivo CCD在我现在所做的事情中也非常活跃
this will give you the bases of the information
这将为您提供信息基础
and then get your license plate decimeter german that you can manage it in west
然后让您的车牌分米德文，您可以在西部进行管理
money in simple things you do is karssen missing you have i done by house martell
你做的简单事情中的钱是卡尔森想念的，你是由马爹利做的
you are going for the sorrow the dongle edges by hans
你正要为汉斯的加密狗边缘感到悲伤
now you do research cm wide and therefore peat center here already very simple
现在您要研究厘米宽，因此这里的泥炭中心已经非常简单
much easier in the traditional stick pack if you can see the olivieri is
如果您看到olivieri是
week ago and really does santing if so your premium to this week so i
一周前，如果确实如此，您的确会感到放心，所以我
hope you like it hot wheel broadcast hi rouge and another fantastic week and
希望你喜欢它的风火轮转播，还有另一个美好的一周，
on the sine cops gent enqueue tanks roberts reminder the after that providing
在正弦警察上，绅士入队坦克罗伯特提醒之后，
financial by geert de sharing what have in a publication mark and always
geert de Sharing所著的《金融》一书在出版标记中总是存在
remember that crypto currency markets always changing it's all i thought
记住，加密货币市场总是在变化，这就是我的想法
bubble aso under your best to live for
尽你所能生存的泡沫麻生太郎